{
  "chapter": 10,
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Cloud Computing concept of delivering infinite resource is achieved by",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Maintaining a huge pool of resources",
        "Workload management",
        "Proper capacity planning",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Over-provisioning of resources in traditional way of capacity planning causes",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Performance degradation",
        "Loss of reputation",
        "Performance enhancement",
        "Wastage of budget"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Under-provisioning of resources in traditional way of capacity planning may cause",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Auto-scaling",
        "Loss of reputation",
        "Performance enhancement",
        "Budget saving"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Availability of infinite resource on-demand in cloud computing is actually an illusion",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True", "False"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Unlike following N + 1 rule of capacity maintenance, cloud service consumers enjoy which among the following facility in capacity maintenance",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "N + X rule",
        "N rule",
        "Infinite resource",
        "Auto-scaling"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Resource utilization curve represents",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Average resource utilization",
        "Total volume of system resources",
        "Resource utilization under load",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "When resource utilization reaches ceiling, that limit is called",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Stress point",
        "Limiting point",
        "End point",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Unlike traditional computing, capacity planning is no more required to avail computing facility in cloud",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True",
        "Required, but much easier",
        "Required, but less risky",
        "Both b and c"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Before capacity enhancement of an application, the capacity planner should know about",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Cost of the additional resources",
        "Value of the added capacity in business",
        "How much resource is required",
        "Both a and c"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "IaaS consumers in cloud, do the capacity planning with",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Virtual resources",
        "Physical resources",
        "Both physical and virtual resources",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the relation of capacity of system with its performance?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Proportional",
        "Reverse",
        "Similar",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    }
  ]
}
